let's look at the answer to our cache
quiz these three are very similar to the
options we have when we want to get
books from a library this is like going
to the library every time we need to
look up something and clearly we don't
want to do that main memory is just like
the library slow and very large so if we
go to the main memory every time we're
spending a lot of time just waiting for
the main memory to respond with data
having the small memory inside the
processor core and bringing the stuff we
access there is the approach of
basically
caching the memory
locations and this is very similar to
borrowing the book from the library so
that we can use it for a while while
we're interested in that topic and then
return it and finally having a huge
memory NEX door processor and then
bringing everything in there is solving
some of the problems of going to the
main memory because this memory is
hopefully somewhat closer to our
processor but this memory is still going
to be large and thus very slow so this
is very similar to just building a
library closer to home yes you are
saving some time on each access but most
of the time that you spend per access is
still there simply because it takes a
while to find data in such a large
memory so caches are exploiting spatial
and temporal locality and overcoming the
problem of having a slow and large main
memory just like borrowing books from
the library is exploiting spatial and
temporal locality and over coming the
problem of accessing a huge Library
slowly